<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Matthew&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Matthew&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>matthew@matthew-greenwood.com (Matthew Greenwood)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>matthew@matthew-greenwood.com (Matthew Greenwood)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unit 1 AI Agent Course</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/unit-1-hf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>matthew@matthew-greenwood.com (Matthew Greenwood)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/unit-1-hf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ai-agents-what-are-they-&#34;&gt;AI Agents: What are they? 🕵🏻&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s be clear off the bat, an AI agent isn&amp;rsquo;t like Agent Smith from the Matrix. Well not yet at least&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An &lt;strong&gt;AI agent&lt;/strong&gt; is essentially a system that can reason, plan, and interact with its environment to achieve a goal set by the user. It&amp;rsquo;s a goal-oriented machine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An agent is made up of two main components. The first is the &lt;strong&gt;LLM&lt;/strong&gt; (Large Language Model), which is the &lt;strong&gt;brain&lt;/strong&gt; of the system. The LLM allows the agent to understand your natural language, handle the reasoning, and plan the actions it will take. The second component is the &lt;strong&gt;body&lt;/strong&gt;—the &lt;strong&gt;tools&lt;/strong&gt; the agent uses to interact with the world. These tools can be simple programs the agent calls upon, or more complex APIs that access real-time data.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My first blog post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/first-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>matthew@matthew-greenwood.com (Matthew Greenwood)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/first-blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello, World! My name is Matthew and this is my first foray into blogging. I am a husband, father, and all around nerd. Never really been one to talk about myself much but hoping this will make it easier to put myself out there for the world to see. I have a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science with emphasis in Game and Simulation Programming and still staying up-to-date on current trends as much as I can. Looking to get my foot in the door in the tech field still as I am very determined to get my career going into full swing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Matthew Greenwood</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>matthew@matthew-greenwood.com (Matthew Greenwood)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m on a dedicated journey to transition into the &lt;strong&gt;tech field&lt;/strong&gt; to follow my lifelong passion for &lt;strong&gt;programming&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For most of my career, I was in &lt;strong&gt;Management&lt;/strong&gt;, where I honed critical skills in problem-solving, project coordination, and operational adaptability—all invaluable for a successful career in software development. My recent career choices have been driven by a commitment to my family, including supporting my mother. Now that I have more time to focus, I&amp;rsquo;m fully dedicating myself to launching my new career path, building a better future for us all. When I&amp;rsquo;m not learning, I&amp;rsquo;m a proud father of two sons and happily married since 2018.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
